<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>post on Jacmoe&#39;s Cyber Soapbox</title>
    <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/categories/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in post on Jacmoe&#39;s Cyber Soapbox</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 02:59:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jacmoe.github.io/categories/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When rodents ate my internet connection</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/when-rodents-ate-my-internet-connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 02:59:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/when-rodents-ate-my-internet-connection/</guid>
      <description>A roof rat peeks out between the railroad ties. (Joshua J. Cotten, Unsplash: https://unsplash.com/photos/QNaBO0oHeyo) In a Vox interview (“Neil Gaiman: Boredom Is a Writer’s Best Friend - Vox” n.d.) Neil Gaiman was asked what advice he would give to beginning writers. And his advice was to get bored. “Ideas come from daydreaming,” he explained. “They come from drifting.”
You have to let yourself get so bored that your mind has nothing better to do than tell itself a story – Neil Gaiman</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Entry in my new Gemini Log</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/first_entry_in_my_new_gemini_log/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/first_entry_in_my_new_gemini_log/</guid>
      <description>First entry in my new Gemlog The first entry of my Gemini Log (Gemlog) is up: 2023-03-17 - Hello, Universe! I am thinking that my Gemini Capsule should be a place for me to share my writing, my writer’s journal, and my musings about writing.
Much simpler to put something up on Gemini: simply write a simple text, and put it on the server.
Here’s to many more entries in the Gemlog!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Gemini Server - Quick and Dirty</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/local_gemini_server_quick_and_dirty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/local_gemini_server_quick_and_dirty/</guid>
      <description>If you, like me, are excited about Project Gemini and want to create your own capsule (Gemini site), you will probably wonder how you would test your capsule on your local machine before putting it out there.
This small (and dirty!) guide aims to remove that doubt.
So, without further dillydally, here goes:
Install GmCapsule by running the following command, assuming that Python is installed:
pip install gmcapsule Now, create a .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
