<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>emacs on Jacmoes Cyber Soapbox</title>
    <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/tags/emacs/</link>
    <description>Jacmoes Cyber Soapbox (emacs)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="https://jacmoe.github.io/tags/emacs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my new blog</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/welcome-to-my-new-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/welcome-to-my-new-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;#+begin_description
My old blog at WordPress only has one single post in it. I wrote it using Org-mode in Emacs, and used an Emacs package to send it to WordPress. And that was good, but the bad thing was that I had to tweak a lot of HTML, obviously putting me off writing blog posts. But now things are changing!
#+end_description]]
&lt;img src=&#34;https://jacmoe.github.io/images/hugoblog.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;
My &lt;a href=&#34;https:/jacmoes.wordpress.com/&#34;&gt;old blog&lt;/a&gt; at WordPress only has one single post in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wrote it using Org-mode in Emacs, and used an extension to put it on WordPress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to perform a lot of tweaking to the HTML, however, and that has obviously put me off just writing blog posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted something as easy as writing a blog post in my favorite writing environment, committing the changes to a git repository, and pushing it to a repository. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to deal with a website like WordPress, to be honest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hugo-and-emacs&#34; &gt;Hugo and Emacs
&lt;span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#hugo-and-emacs&#34;&gt;
        &lt;svg viewBox=&#34;0 0 28 23&#34; height=&#34;100%&#34; width=&#34;19&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34;&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 13a5 5 0 0 0 7.54.54l3-3a5 5 0 0 0-7.07-7.07l-1.72 1.71&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-miterlimit=&#34;10&#34; stroke-width=&#34;2&#34;/&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M14 11a5 5 0 0 0-7.54-.54l-3 3a5 5 0 0 0 7.07 7.07l1.71-1.71&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-miterlimit=&#34;10&#34; stroke-width=&#34;2&#34;/&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After hunting around, I stumbled over a good workflow using &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo &lt;/a&gt; and the excellent Emacs extension &lt;code&gt;ox-hugo&lt;/code&gt;.
All I have to do is write my blog posts in one org-file within Emacs, export to Hugo using the exporter, and let Hugo generate the output. Then I commit the changes to my git repository, push it to GitHub, and my homepage is updated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have to mess around with anything, like I did in WordPress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since it&amp;rsquo;s now going to be much easier to get a blog post up, I am sure I will actually blog a post or two now :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have several ideas, and the good thing about it is, that I can have those posts in my org-file, as sub-trees, because the &lt;a href=&#34;https://ox-hugo.scripter.co/&#34;&gt;Emacs Hugo exporter&lt;/a&gt; will only export the trees that are &lt;code&gt;DONE&lt;/code&gt;, not the ones marked with &lt;code&gt;TODO&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It should be easy to blog, and I am most comfortable in Emacs. So, there&amp;rsquo;s that :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
