<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jacmoe&#39;s Cyber Soapbox</title>
    <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jacmoe&#39;s Cyber Soapbox</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:38:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jacmoe.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 01:34:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/about/about/</guid>
      <description>testing On the other hand, we denounce with righteous indignation and dislike men who are so beguiled and demoralized by the charms of pleasure of the moment, so blinded by desire, that they cannot foresee the pain and trouble that are bound to ensue; and equal blame belongs to those who fail in their duty through weakness of will, which is the same as saying through shrinking from toil and pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:38:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/gallery/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:38:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/gallery/gallery/</guid>
      <description>Hotel California of Creative Writing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Entry in my new Gemini Log</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/first_entry_in_my_new_gemini_log/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/first_entry_in_my_new_gemini_log/</guid>
      <description>First entry in my new Gemlog The first entry of my Gemini Log (Gemlog) is up: 2023-03-17 - Hello, Universe! I am thinking that my Gemini Capsule should be a place for me to share my writing, my writer’s journal, and my musings about writing.
Much simpler to put something up on Gemini: simply write a simple text, and put it on the server.
Here’s to many more entries in the Gemlog!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Gemini Server - Quick and Dirty</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/local_gemini_server_quick_and_dirty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/local_gemini_server_quick_and_dirty/</guid>
      <description>If you, like me, are excited about Project Gemini and want to create your own capsule (Gemini site), you will probably wonder how you would test your capsule on your local machine before putting it out there.
This small (and dirty!) guide aims to remove that doubt.
So, without further dillydally, here goes:
Install GmCapsule by running the following command, assuming that Python is installed:
pip install gmcapsule Now, create a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my new blog</title>
      <link>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/welcome-to-my-new-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:50:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacmoe.github.io/posts/welcome-to-my-new-blog/</guid>
      <description>My new Emacs powered blog My old blog at WordPress only has one single post in it.
I wrote it using Org-mode in Emacs, and used an extension to put it on WordPress.
That was good.
I had to perform a lot of tweaking to the HTML, however, and that has obviously put me off just writing blog posts.
That was bad.
So, I wanted something as easy as writing a blog post in my favorite writing environment, committing the changes to git source control, and pushing it to a remote repository to be hosted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
